你是我的阳光
You are my sunshine
我唯一的阳光
My only sunshine
你让我感到愉快
You make me happy
即使天空阴郁
When skies are grey
你永远不会了解
You'll never know, dear
我有多么爱你
How much I love you
请别带走我的阳光
Please don't take my sunshine away
有天晚上
The other night, dear
我睡着时
As I was sleeping
梦到我抱着你
I dreamed I held you in my arms
可我醒来
When I awoke, dear
才发觉这是个梦
I was mistaken
为此我低头哭泣
And I hung my head and I cried
你曾告诉我 亲爱的
You told me once, dear
你真的爱我
You really loved me
而且没人能
And no one else could
从中妨碍
come between
但现在你离我而去
But now you left me
爱上另一位
To love another
从而粉碎了我所有的梦境
You have shattered all my dreams
你是我的阳光
You are my sunshine,
我唯一的阳光
My only sunshine
你让我感到愉快
You make me happy
即使天空阴郁
When skys are grey
你永远不会了解
You'll never know, dear
我有多么爱你
How much I love you
请别带走我的阳光
Please don't take my sunshine away